# Josh Davey

## Personal Statement:

## Designer, Developer, Photographer

Creativity, commitment and passion are three key characteristics that describe me.

After several years working as a freelance photographer, I have spent over 3 years expanding my creative skillset through study. Through this I have discovered a passion for digital development, from the creative to the technical.

I enjoy the creative freedom of design and bringing a story to life through creative means. On the technical side, building websites and programs that improve the lives of others is something that I find fascinating and am looking for opportunities to be part of teams that do this.

I'm looking for a role where I can utilise and grow my exising web and graphic deisgn skills, as well as working in a team that produces meaningful work that improves the world around us.

## **Education:**

Yoobee Colleges: July 2018 - Dec 2021

- Level 6 Diploma in Web & UX Design UI & UX Design, Foundation Coding, App Development, CMS
- Level 6 Diploma in Creative Digital Design Branding, Information Design, Packaging Design, Event Design
- Level 5 Diploma in Web & Graphic Design UI Design, UX Testing, Illustration, Branding

## **Experience:**

- Freelance Photographer & Graphic Designer at 9nth 2015 - Current: Commercial photography work for Merrell, Rains, Mountain Designs & Lander. Branding and Web Design for Consillio.
- Kitchen Hand at Ibis Hotel Wellington Feb 2021 - Current: Plating desserts, food preparation & cleaning.
- **Produce Assistant at New World** Sept 2017 - Feb 2021: Stocking of shelves, cleaning & food preperation.
- Community Manager at OzShot Magazine 2016 - 2017: Social media & content management, hosting community events, publishing articles.

## References:

Jessica Bay

Team Leader: Creative Digital Design & Tutor at Yoobee Colleges + 64 21 079 7829 jessica.bay@yoobeecolleges.com

## Contact:

022 041 5434

Be behance.net/joshdavey

instagram.com/9nth

### Soft Skills:

- Creative Thinking
- **Passionate**
- Collaborative
- Time Management
- Verbal Communication
- Empathetic

### **Technical Skills:**

- **HTML & CSS**
- **JavaScript**
- **Back End Basics**
- **Responsive Design**
- Wordpress
- Adobe Suite
- Figma

#### Matthew O'Keefe

Web Developer & Owner at Consillio + 64 21 111 0203 okeefe.matthew@gmail.com